(Applause)
(تصفيق)
Thank you.
شكرا لكم
(Music)
(موسيقى)
♫ Slide into the shimmering surface ♫
♫انزلق الى سطح متلألئ♫
♫ between two worlds. ♫
♫بين عالمين♫
♫ Standing at the center of time ♫
♫اقف في مركز الزمن♫
♫ as it uncurls. ♫
♫ المتخلص من تجاعيده ♫
♫ Cutting through the veil of illusion. ♫
♫مخترقا حاجز الخيال♫
♫ Moving beyond past conclusions. ♫
♫متخطيا استنتاجات الماضي♫
♫ Wondering if all my doubt and confusion will clear. ♫
♫متسائلا اذا ما كنت كل شكوكي وحيرتي سوف تنجلي♫
♫ If I could be anywhere, ♫
♫لو كان بامكاني التواجد في مكان اخر♫
♫ if I could be anywhere, ♫
♫ لو كان بامكاني التواجد في مكان اخر♫
♫ if I could be anywhere right now, ♫
♫ لو كان بامكاني التواجد في مكان اخر الان ♫
♫ I would want to be here. ♫
♫ لكنت اخترت ان ا كون هنا ♫
♫ Searching for the future ♫
♫ ابحث عن المستقبل ♫
♫ among the things we're throwing away. ♫
♫ في الاشياء التي نلقيها ♫
♫ Trying to see the world ♫
♫ محاولا رؤية العالم ♫
♫ through the junk we produce everyday. ♫
♫ خلال المخلفات التي ننتجها كل يوم ♫
♫ They say nothing lasts forever, ♫
♫ يقولون انا لا شيئ يبقى للابد ♫
♫ but all the plastic ever made is still here. ♫
♫ لكن جميع البلاسيتك الذي صنعناه لا يزال موجود هنا ♫
♫ And no amount of closing our eyes ♫
♫ واغلاق اعيننا لاي وقت ♫
♫ will make it disappear. ♫
♫ لن يجعله يختفي ♫
♫ If I could be anywhere, ♫
♫لو كان بامكاني التواجد في مكان اخر♫
♫ if I could be anywhere in history, ♫
♫لو كان بامكاني التواجد في مكان اخر في التاريخ ♫
♫ I would want to be here. ♫
♫ لكنت اخترت ان اكون هنا ♫
♫ The Romans, the Spanish ♫
♫ الرومان , الاسبان ♫
♫ the British, the Dutch, ♫
♫ البريطانيين , الدنماركيين ♫
♫ American exceptionalism, so out of touch. ♫
♫ الاستثنائيون الامريكييون, بعيدة المنال ♫
♫ The folly of empire repeating its course, ♫
♫ حماقة الامبراطورية التي تكرر نفس المنهج ♫
♫ imposing its will ♫
♫ فارضة ارادتها ♫
♫ and ruling by force ♫
♫ وتحكم بالقوة ♫
♫ on and on through time. ♫
♫ مرارا وتكرارا مع مرور الزمن♫
♫ But the world can't take it very much longer. ♫
♫ لكن العالم لم يعد قادر على التحمل لمدة اطول ♫
♫ We're not going to make it ♫
♫ لن نتمكن من عمله ♫
♫ unless we're smarter and stronger. ♫
♫ الا اذا كنا اذكى واقوى ♫
♫ The world is going to shake itself free of our greed ♫
♫ سينتفض العالم متخلصا من جشعنا ♫
♫ somehow. ♫
♫ بطريقة ما ♫
♫ If I could be anywhere, ♫
♫لو كان بامكاني التواجد في مكان اخر♫
♫ if I could be anywhere in time, ♫
♫ لو كان بامكاني التواجد في مكان اخر في الزمن ♫
♫ if I could be anywhere and change things, ♫
♫ لو كان بامكاني التواجد في مكان اخر واغير الاشياء ♫
♫ it would have to be now. ♫
♫ يجب ان يكون الان ♫
♫ They say nothing last forever, ♫
♫ يقولون لا شيئ يبقى للابد ♫
♫ but all the plastic ever made is still here. ♫
♫ لكن جميع البلاستيك الذي صنعناه لا يزال موجود هنا ♫
♫ And no amount of closing our eyes ♫
♫ واغلاق اعيننا لاي وقت ♫
♫ will make it disappear. ♫
♫ لن يجعله يختفي ♫
♫ And the world can't take it ♫
♫ ولن يتحمله العالم ♫
♫ very much longer. ♫
♫ لفترة اطول ♫
♫ We're not going to make it ♫
♫ لن نتمكن من عمله ♫
♫ unless we're smarter and stronger. ♫
♫ الا اذا كنا اذكى واقوى ♫
♫ The world's gonna shake itself free of our greed ♫
♫ سينتفض العالم متخلصا من جشعنا ♫
♫ somehow. ♫
♫ بطريقة ما ♫
♫ And the world can't take it, that you can see. ♫
♫ العالم لن يتحمله , يبدو ذلك واضحا ♫
♫ If the oceans don't make it, neither will we. ♫
♫ اذا لم تقم بذلك المحيطات , فلن نفعل ذلك نحن ايضا ♫
♫ The world's gonna shake itself all the way free ♫
♫ سوف يهز العالم نفسه في سبيل الحرية "
♫ somehow. ♫
♫ بطريقة ما ♫
♫ If I could be anywhere, ♫
♫ لو كان بامكاني التواجد في مكان اخر♫
♫ if I could be anywhere in time, ♫
♫ لو كان بامكاني التواجد في مكان اخر في الزمن♫
♫ if I could be anywhere and change the outcome, ♫
♫ لو كان بامكاني التواجد في مكان اخر واغير النتائج ♫
♫ it would have to be now. ♫
♫ يجب ان يكون ذلك الان ♫
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
Thank you.
شكرا لكم